Contact

Estonia, Tallinn +372 53988147 (Mobile) aleksei.gaile@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aleksei-gaile (LinkedIn)

gaile.asuscomm.com (Portfolio) github.com/GaileAlex (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Java

Software Development Spring Framework

Languages

Russian (Native or Bilingual) English (Limited Working)

Certifications

Noorem tarkvaraarendaja, tase 4

Aleksei Gaile

Software Developer at Wisercat. Open for new opportunities. Tallinn

Summary

I am a Java Developer aiming to create quality products and constantly evolving.

I have experience in developing complex web applications, optimizing existing software solutions.

During work participated in three projects, where solved various tasks on the front-end and back-end, and also helped other developers. Prefer to work with the back-end. Java forever!

The motive for changing jobs is the desire for professional development and low workload.

Experience

Wisercat

Junior Software Developer September 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Tallinn, Harjumaa, Estonia

- Development of a web application with a microservice architecture for collecting, processing and analyzing statistical data.
- Stack: Java 8, Spring, Hibernate / JPA, PostgreSQL, Cassandra, Spark, Elasticsearch, OLAP, Liquibase, Docker, Maven, Gradle, Liferay, React, Angular.
- Development of new application functionality
- Solving current tasks on the backend and frontend
- Refactoring of the existing code in accordance with the changing wishes of the client.
- SQL queries to databases.
- Integration and Unit testing using junit, mockito.

LLC "Impulse" Deputy Director, Co-Founder 2012 - 2017 (5 years)

Saint Petersburg, Russian Federation

Construction company

Progress:

- Independently created a company website.
- Created a network and electronic document management.
- Increased the company's revenue more than four times.
- Established relationships with suppliers.
- Increased the number of regular customers.

Education

Ida-Virumaa Kutsehariduskeskus

Secondary education, Software Developer · (2017 - 2019)

"Status"

Courses, Network administrator (Windows Server). · (2010 - 2010)

Baltic State Technical University "VOENMEH" named after D.F. Ustinov

Master's degree, Rocket engine mechanical engineer. (1990 - 1996)